you put a woman into a coma.
你使这个女人处于昏迷状态
Surely that arouses some kind of emotion.
当然会引起情感波动
Well, it doesn't.
这不会的
You and I are finished.
你我之间没有关系了
One said goodbye...
一个说了再见
I'm so tired of feeling like a failure.
我受够了这种失败的生活
One almost lost it...
一个几乎死去
And one got exactly
当然还有一个...
Gabrielle was waiting for her next great idea.
Gabrielle准备她下一个的伟大计划
Her first great idea came when she was 15,
当她15岁时  她想出了第1个伟大计划
after her stepfather paid her a late-night visit.
在她继父为能半夜来她房间 付给她钱后
She bought a bus ticket to New York the very next day.
第2天就买了车票跑到了纽约
Her next occurred five years later when she decided to seduce a famous fashion photographer.
她第2个是在5年后当她决定勾引 一个有名的时装摄影师
One week later, she began her career as a runway model,
一周后  她开始了她的模特生涯
which soon led to her next great idea --
没过多久又有了下一个计划
her decision to marry Carlos Solis.
她决定嫁给 Carlos Solis
Before she knew it, she had jumped off the runway and moved to the suburbs.
她不再作模特  而是搬到了郊区
Her most recent great idea was born out of her boredom with her new life.
她最近的计划怎么摆脱她现在的生活
That's how she came to start an affair with her teenage gardener,
所以她开始和那个年轻园丁混在一起
which was cut short by a tragic accident,
但因为一次意外而结束
so once again, Gabrielle was in need of a great idea.
所以Gabrielle又有了一个新的主意
Mrs. Solis, I know you're worried, but it's going to take time.
Solis夫人  我知道你很担心 但是还得有一段时间才能恢复
Hmm?
嗯?
What is?
什么？
You look sad.
你看起来很伤心
I assume you're thinking about your mother-in-law.
我想你一定在担心你的婆婆
Oh, no.
哦  不是
So, uh, what were you thinking about?
那你在想什么呢？
My life.
我的生活
It hasn't turned out like I thought it would.
生活并我像我想的那样
Oh, honey.
噢 亲爱的
Oh, no, I-I know I shouldn't complain.
噢  不  我知道我不该抱怨
It's just there's something missing, and I don't know what it is.
我总觉的少点什么？ 可是却不知道是什么？
Do you ever feel that way?
你有那样的感觉吗？
Mm, no.
恩  没有
When I go home at night, I sleep like a baby,
当我晚上回家  我睡的就像小孩一样死
'cause I know I did something that day that helped people.
因为我知道今天我帮了很多人
That must be a nice feeling.
那一定感觉很好
Hmm. It is.
恩  是的
Of course, there's times I wish I didn't have to work so hard.
不过  有时候我希望 不要工作太累了
We've got a real nursing shortage here, and they keep cutting our budget and --
我们这很缺护士  但是他们还是减工资
Attention, all available personnel --
注意  所有人注意
code blue, stat, room 214.
蓝色警报  214房间
Excuse me.
对不起
Attention, all available personnel --
注意  所有人注意
code blue, stat, room 214.
蓝色警报  214房间
Damn it, get a doctor in here! I don't have an airway.
见鬼  快去叫医生  我这没有氧气罩
No time. I have to intubate.
没时间了  我不得不把气管插进去
Mr. Getz? Mr. Getz, listen.
Getz先生  Getz先生  听我说
You're not dying on me, okay?
你别吓我  好吗？
This tube is to help you breathe.
这个管子能帮你呼吸
I need you to be brave now.
我需要你呼吸
It was then that Gabrielle got her next great idea.
这是Gabrielle又有了一个主意
She decided to throw the first annual Sacred Heart charity fashion show to raise money for more nursing staff.
她准备开一场慈善时装表演 来为护士们捐款
Gabby, Gabby, I can't do it.
Gabby  Gabby  我做不来
I cannot walk down a runway in one of these dresses.
我不能穿这些裙子走在舞台上
They all make me look so fat.
我穿它们显的太胖
Please get someone to take my place. Please.
还是让别人替我吧
- Betty, listen to me.
- Betty  听我说
No, no, please
不 不
listen, Betty, okay?
听我说  Betty  好吗？
You're not quitting on me now.
你现在不能退出
We're going to find you a gown.
我们重新给你找一件长裙
It's going to be black and slimming, and you're going to look great.
它会使你显的很苗条而且漂亮
I need you to be brave now.
我需要你鼓起勇气
Okay.
好吧
And that night, when she went to bed, Gabrielle slept like a baby.
在那天晚上  Gabrielle睡的非常香
News of the fashion show spread quickly on Wisteria Lane.
这场时装表演很快在Wisteria Lane传开了
Though the event was for charity,
尽管是慈善的活动
Gabrielle soon discovered when it came to the latest fashions,
Gabrielle不久发现最新款的时装...
women are seldom charitable.
女人们很少有捐出来
No one knew this better than Edie Britt.
没有人比Edie Britt懂行
She understood that treachery never goes out of style.
她知道这些衣服并不过时
Susan.
Susan
Give me the dress.
给我这个裙子
I gave it a shot.
我只是看看
Hi, Helen.
嘿  Helen
Hi.
嘿
How's the dress fitting?
裙子还合身吧
Great. Maybe it could be taken out in the shoulder a little.
不错  就是肩膀这有点问题
Sure, no problem.
当然  没问题
There you go.
马上好
You know, Gabrielle, I-I never thanked you properly.
你知道吗  Gabrielle  我还没谢你呢
For what?
为什么？
For what you did for my son.
谢谢你为我儿子做的
It was so nice of you to hire John as your gardener.
非常高兴你雇我的儿子做你的园丁
Believe me, it's been my pleasure.
相信我   这是我应该做的
How's he doing?
他做的怎么样？
Good. Good.
好  好
I hear he's dating Danielle Van De Kamp.
我听说他在和Danielle Van De Kamp约会
Oh, for now. I think it's just a matter of time before they break up for good.
就现在来看  我觉得他们迟早要分手
What's wrong?
怎么回事？
Oh, she just seems to want much more of a relationship than he does.
噢  她好象还有别的企图
You remember what it was like dating teenage boys.
你还记得吗和男孩们约会的情形吗？
V aguely.
都忘了
Thank you.
谢谢你
No, you tell that son of a bitch Tanaka that if he doesn't call me in an hour,
你告诉那个Tanaka  如果他不在1小时后 给我打电话...
I'm going to go down to his office, find him, and kick his ass.
我就去他办公室找他  好好揍他一顿
Ladies.
女士们
Trouble at work?
工作有问题？
I don't know what his problem is.
我不知道他有什么问题
He's making money left and right.
总之他在赚钱
I just wish he'd relax.
我就是希望他能休息会
Crap, crap, crap.
太烂了  太烂了  太烂了
I'm telling you, all of the good dresses are taken.
我告诉你们  所有的好衣服都被买走了
Now what the hell am I supposed to wear?
那我现在该穿什么呢？
Why don't you wear this one?
为什么不试试这件？
This is an old lady dress.
这是给老太太穿的
You won't even be able to see my body.
你甚至都看不见我的身体
That is so like you, Edie. You're always thinking of others.
Edie  这非常适合你 你总是替别人着想
So why isn't Mrs. Huber here?
那么Huber夫人怎么没来呢？
Last I heard, she went to visit her sister.
我听说  她去看她的姐姐了
I just can't believe that Martha would agree to wear this.
我不敢相信Martha决定穿这件衣服
She always said she'd never be caught dead in black.
她总是说她讨厌黑色的
Sadly for Mrs. Huber,
Huber夫人就惨了
this was no longer the case.
在没有比这惨了
Hey, mom.
嘿  妈妈
Julie, you'll never guess who you got a letter from.
Julie  你绝对猜不到谁给我来信了
Zach. Isn't that weird --him writing you?
Zach  很奇怪他会给你写信？
Yeah.
是的
Well, open. Open, open, open.
快点   打开
He -- he could have said something about Dana.
他可能说了一些关于Dana的事情
I'll read it later.
我晚点在看
Later? What's wrong with now?
晚点？  现在怎么不行？
I've got tons of homework, mom.
我有许多作业要做
Julie, what's going on?
Julie　　怎么回事？
This isn't the first letter I've gotten from Zach.
这已经不是第１次收到Zach的信了
We've been writing each other the last couple of weeks.
我们通信有一段时间了
Are you mad?
你生气了吗？
No.
没有
Just when I was your age, my pen pal lived on a farm in Ohio, not in a mental institution.
当我还是你这么大的时候我的笔友住在 Ohio的一个农场里　而不在精神病院
You know, that letter is one notch above prison mail.
你知道吗　那种信比监狱来的信都可怕
Zach's not crazy.
Zach没有发疯
He's just upset over his mom, and his dad doesn't even seem to care.
他只是为她母亲的事情伤心 而他的父亲也不怎么关心
He just needs a friend.
他就是需要一个朋友
I packed the diapers,
我来换尿布
I'm getting the juice boxes and the carrot sticks --
我拿上果汁和胡箩卜
sunscreen?
防晒霜
Got it.
知道了
I go pick up the boys, we hit the park,
我去接孩子　我们公园见
and that should give you a good couple of hours.
那就能给你几个小时的时间
Enjoy the vacation.
享受假期吧
What?
什么？
While you're gone, I'll be here paying bills and sorting laundry and cooking dinner,
你走后  我还要付帐单  叠衣服和做晚饭
so what part of that sounds like a vacation?
那怎么能算假期呢？
Okay, right, you know what? We'll pick up dinner.
好吧  你知道吗？ 我们一起出去吃饭
and you just take a hot bath, relax, recharge.
你只需要洗个热水澡  放松一下
Okay, I get it.
好吧  我明白
It's going to take more than a hot bath to recharge,
这不是洗个澡就能恢复过来的
but, uh, don't forget, I'm here all week.
但是别忘了  我一周都在这
Then what?
那又怎么样呢？
And then we go back to normal?
我们还能回到过去正常的生活吗
Tom, our last version of normal had me popping pills.
Tom  我们最后的正常生活是吃避孕药
Normal is a bad, bad plan.
恢复正常是个很烂的计划
Okay, so we'll put our heads together, and we'll come up with a solution.
好吧  我们同心协力把问题解决
I think we need to hire a nanny full-time.
我想我们得请个全值保姆
That's just such a big, big commitment.
那可是个大问题
I know, and I know we can't afford it,
我知道我们负担不起
and I know everything that's happened is my fault,
我想一切都是我的错
but if I don't get some help,
但如果我不帮忙
there's an excellent chance I will lose my mind.
这有个好机会可以让我轻松下来
Okay, well, then, we have to make it work.
好  那我们就请一个
Next up, the 200-meter freestyle.
下来  200米自由泳
It's just not right.
有点不对劲
What?
怎么了？
A woman is in a coma because of Andrew, and there he is, happy as a clam.
那个女人还在昏迷中 而他却跟没事人一样
Well, we grounded him, we took away the tv in his room.
我们已经惩罚他了 我们把他的电视拿走了
How many more ways you want to punish him?
你还想怎么惩罚他呢？
Swimmers, take your marks.
选手们  准备
I think we should make him quit the swim team.
我想我应该让他悄悄的退出游泳队
Bree, this is the one thing in his life that he's passionate about.
Bree  他也就这点爱好了
Well, maybe if we take it away from him, then he'll start to understand what he did.
或许我们把它从他身边拿走 他就会有所反醒
He has not shown an ounce of remorse since the accident.
他对那次意外没有一点自责
Of course he feels bad.
他当然有了
He's just, you know, keeping up a facade.
他只是勇敢面对
Well, he's doing a fabulous job.
是的  他做的非常好
Look, if we take him off the swim team,
听着  如果我们让他退出游泳队
he'll lose his shot at an athletic scholarship,
他可能就没有体育奖学金了
and then he's never going to forgive us.
那样他是不会原谅我们的
Well, if it ensures he grows up with some trace of humanity, then that's a risk I am willing to take.
如果那样可以让他有点人味的话 我愿意冒这个险
Well, I'm not.
我不会
That's because you just don't love him as much as I do.
那是因为你不在像我这么爱他了
Well, isn't that nice?
你那样就好吗？
It's just a fact. I'm his mother.
那是事实  我是他母亲
He lived inside of me.
是我生了他
He hung out in your womb for a few months back in the '80s.
他只是在80年代在你的子宫待了几个月
Since then, I have grown to love him just as much as you.
从那以后  我就像你一样爱他
What just happened?
发生什么事情了？
That kid you both love so much just won the race.
那个你们都爱的孩子赢了比赛
John.
John
My mom said you needed volunteers, so I volunteered.
我母亲说你需要志愿者  所以我来了
Oh.
噢
Finally got the charity bug?
终于得到了点施舍
You sound surprised.
你听起来感觉很吃惊
No, not really.
不  没有
You were always a giver.
你是那个给予者
Would you knock it off?
你能别说那事吗？
My mom's right over there.
我妈妈就在那
Have a seat.
请坐
You can start by helping us alphabetize the donation cards.
你可以按字母顺序排列这些捐款卡片
So word on the street is you and Danielle might break up.
小道消息你和Danielle要分手了
Maybe. I don't know.
可能吧  我不知道
Is that because of me?
那是因为我吗？
Not everything is about you.
并不都是你的原因
Would you stop that?
你可以不要这样做吗
Have you been thinking about me?
你有没有想我
No.
没有
Really?
是吗？
Could have fooled me.
你敢骗我
Hey, do you need any help?
嘿  要帮忙吗？
Please. Just pull up a chair.
请给我拿把椅子
Oh, gosh.
哦  天那
That's okay. I got it.
没事  我来拿
Ow! Oh!
噢
Susan, hi.
Susan  嘿
Do you want to help with the seating cards?
你能帮我弄那些座位卡片吗？
Sure. Do you want to tell me why you had your foot in John Rowland's crotch yesterday?
当然  你能告诉我昨天为什么你把你的脚 放在John Rowland大腿上
Oh, that.
噢  那个啊
Uh, he was helping me adjust the seam in my stocking,
噢  他在帮我缝我的丝袜
and from your angle, it must have looked a little weird.
从你的角度看去当然奇怪了
You're sleeping with him, aren't you?
你和他睡过觉  是吗？
Okay.
是的
Yes, but you have to promise not to tell anybody.
是的  但是保证不要把此事告诉别人
Gabrielle, he's in high school, and it's illegal, and you're married.
Gabrielle  他还在上高中 那样做是违法的  而且你还有老公
If Carlos found out, this would kill him.
如果Carlos发现了  Carlos会杀了他的
It's just sex. It's totally harmless.
仅仅是发生性关系  没关系的
How can you call something like this harmless?
你怎么能说没关系呢？
After everything you know about what I went through with Karl?
你是知道我和Karl最后的结果
This isn't about you.
这和你无关
Yes, it is.
当然有关
It's about me and about every other person who was screwed over by somebody they loved.
我和其他那些别自己爱的人抛弃的人 都有关系
When Karl ran off with Brandi, you saw what a basket case I was.
当Karl和Brandi跑了 你知道我那时的情况
I was crying, I-I was tearing up his clothes. I couldn't get out of bed all day.
我一直哭  我用他的衣服擦眼泪 我一整天都不能下床
You were right there. How could you do the same thing?
你当时也在那  你怎么能做同样的事呢？
Okay, how can you compare me to Karl? That's not fair.
你怎么能拿我和Karl比较？ 那样不公平
You have no idea what my life is like.
你不知道我的处境
Well, why don't you enlighten me?
好啊  那你给我说说是怎么回事？
You're beautiful, you have more money than you can spend,
你很漂亮  有很多钱
and you have a husband who adores you.
还有一个爱你的老公
No, he doesn't adore me.
不  他不爱我
He adores having me.
他喜欢拥有我
That's a rationalization, and you know it.
那也很合理的  你是明白的
See you at the show.
演出时见
Okay, honey. There you go.
宝贝  到这来
How many nannies did you interview?
你已经面试了多少个保姆了？
10. 10, each one more incompetent than the last.
10个 一个比一个差劲
One actually asked me --
一个还问我...
there you go --
好了...
if she was expected to change diapers.
她是不是要换尿布
Good nannies are so hard to find.
找个好保姆真是太难了
Yeah, that's why I was hoping to take advantage of your expertise.
所以我想听听你的建议
Oh, lord. What do you want me to do?
噢  天那  你想让我干什么？
All your rich friends have nannies -- A-list nannies.
你的有钱朋友都有保姆 一大堆的名单
I need to catch one --
我需要一个...
here you go --
拿好了...
without their bosses.
而不通过她们的老板
Why?
为什么？
So I can poach me one.
所以我才可以请她啊
Lynette --
Lynette
look, at my old job, we didn't wait for good people to come to us.
听着  我原来的公司 从来不等顾客上门
We went out and raided other companies.
我们走出去 去抢别的公司的顾客
I don't see why it should be different when you're hiring a nanny.
我看不出这和请保姆有什么不同
I understand that good help is hard to find, but stealing a family's nanny is so unseemly.
我明白一个好保姆很难找 但是抢别人家的保姆看起来不体面
I'm not twisting anyone's arm.
我又不是威胁人家
If I make a better offer, why shouldn't a qualified person reap the benefits?
如果我给的钱多  难道会没人来吗
So come on.
拜托
Where can I score some high-grade nanny?
我在哪能找到高级点的保姆
Hey, Mrs. Solis.
嘿  Solis夫人
I have some awesome news.
我有一些可怕的消息
I have some not-so-awesome news, so you go first.
我也有一些不太恐怖的消息 所以你先说吧
Broke it off with Danielle.
我和Danielle分手了
I passed her a note during French class.
在法语课上给她写了纸条
So we can be together.
所以我们可以在一起了
John, your timing is impeccable.
John  看来你不走运
What do you mean?
你什么意思？
Susan Mayer saw us last night, and she knows everything.
Susan Mayer昨晚看到咱俩了 她知道了一切事情
Since the accident, Bree had started to worry her son's sense of morality was going up in smoke.
自从那件事以后  Bree开始担心他儿子 的道德感会变的越来越少
She was right to be concerned.
她现在要开始重视了
Andrew?
Andrew？
Can I come in?
我能进来吗？
Uh, yeah, just a sec.
是的  等会
Hey.
嘿
What's up?
怎么了？
Why are you smiling?
为什么你要笑？
Um, it's just a...
那只是...
joke that I heard.
我刚听了一个笑话
Oh. What was it about?
噢  关于什么的？
Well, it's kind of dirty, mom.
算了  是成人笑话  妈妈
Charming.
非常好
What I was wondering is if you've bothered to spend any time reflecting on the reasons
我在想你也许应该多花点时间去反省一下
that you've been grounded and all the pain
...你所做的一切
that you've caused the Solis family.
你给Solis一家带来得痛苦
Yeah, I-I totally get how my actions have affected, like, everything else.
当然我早意识到了我所做的一切 会造成的影响
Really?
真的吗？
Uh-huh.
恩
I-I mean, you know, like when I do something like I did,
我的意思  你知道的 我有时侯做事还像个孩子
and, you know, you got to do something like you did,
你知道吗 你有时侯做事可能也像个孩子
which is --which is, you know, it's -- it's cool,
我的意思是  你知道的  那在所难免
because, um... then everything just kind of balances itself out and --
因为  恩...所有事情都有个平衡点
and goes all smooth again, you know?
一切都会好的  你知道吗
No, I don't.
不  我不明白
What's that smell?
那是什么味道？
Have you been smoking marijuana?
你在吸大麻吗？
No, of course not.
当然没有
You are strung out.
你上瘾了
No. No, no, no, mom.
不  不  不  不  妈妈
Excuse me.
打扰一下
What's that?
那是什么
It's the container you'll be urinating into. Come on.
你往这个容器里尿尿  过来
Ow, ow. Ow, that hurts.
啊  那很疼的
Dr. Sicher. What are you doing here?
Sicher医生  你在这做什么？
Mr. Young, I --
Young先生  我...
I didn't want to upset you by telling you over the phone.
我不想在电话上说这些让你心烦的话
What is it?
那是什么？
Zach is missing from Silvercrest.
Zach从Silvercrest跑了
It happened yesterday evening.
昨天晚上发生的
We think it happened during the shift change.
我们觉得可能是在换班的时候发生的
I know this is difficult to hear.
我知道这很难接受
I'm sorry.
非常抱歉
Yeah, well, it's, uh... just been one of those days.
好吧  我已经习惯了
I still don't get why you're not with Danielle anymore.
我始终不明白你为什么和Danielle分手
She looked so slutty at Ray's party.
在Ray的舞会上她那么的性感
She's not my type, I guess.
我想她可能不是我喜欢的那种类型
What, oh, you still hung upon your mysterious married lady?
不会吧 你还和那个神秘的已婚女人在一起
What is it with her?
她有什么好的？
Besides the obvious, of course.
当然除了她的身材
We talk about real stuff, you know?
我们说点实话吧  你知道吗？
She doesn't treat me like some lame yard boy.
她对我不像对那种乳臭未干小孩一样
But you are a lame yard boy.
但你就是乳臭未干小孩
It's all messed up now anyway.
现在是一团糟了
Her friend found out about us.
她的朋友发现了我们之间的事情
If it gets out, her husband's going to kill me.
如果被传出去  他的丈夫会杀了我的
Huh. But on the upside, your social status at school is going to explode
嘿  好的一面是  你在学校的知名度 可是提高了不少
when people find out you're doing a hot housewife.
当他们知道 你和一个性感家庭主妇混在一起
Shut up, dude.
闭嘴  老兄
Please explain to me how he could just walk out.
请给我解释他怎么能跑了呢？
With the money that I pay you people, I think you could afford a pad lock.
我既然付钱给你们 你们就应该看好他
With all due respect, we are not a high-security facility,
但说起来我们又不是保安公司
and you have restricted our ability to treat Zach.
你只是给了我们治疗Zach的权利
What the hell does that mean?
你那是什么意思？
You've insisted we medicate him without psycho therapy.
你坚持不让我们给他做心理治疗
That is a recipe for disaster.
这本来是很好的治疗方法
Zach is a troubled young man,
Zach是一个极不稳定的青年人
and he's getting progressively worse.
他可能会变的更遭
Hungry?
饿了吗？
I'm starving.
我都快饿死了
Bree had given Lynette the low down on Valley View Park.
Bree让Lynette去Valley View公园
It was a gathering place for up scale nannies and their young charges.
那里有是高级保姆和孩子们聚集的地方
It was Lynette's first time there, and she was determined not to go home alone.
Lynette第一次去那  她不想一个人回家
Of course, Lynette had high standards,
当然  Lynette的要求非常高
so making a connection...
用目光交流
wasn't easy.
并不简单
Still, she was desperate to find that special someone.
她急切的想找一个特殊的保姆
And that's exactly who she found.
那就是她要找的人
Wash your hands. Okay.
请把你的手洗一下  好了
All righty. Here's one for you and one for Amy.
好了  这个给你  这个给Amy
All right, have fun, and I'll be right here if you need me, okay?
那好好玩把  我就在这 有什么需要就来找我 好吗？
From the moment she saw her...
当她看到她的那一刻起
is this seat taken?
这有人吗？
No. Go ahead.
没有  你坐吧
Lynette knew she had to have her.
Lynette知道就是她了
You know, I couldn't help but notice how wonderful you are with those children.
你知道吗  我感到非常惊奇 你和这些孩子这么融洽
Thanks.
谢谢
I'm Lynette.
我是Lynette
Claire.
Claire
Claire?
Claire？
Always loved that name.
我一直都很喜欢那个名字
So, Claire
那么  Claire
do you come here often?
你常来这吗？
What's this?
这是什么？
Your son's urine.
你儿子的尿
I'm going to need a moment.
等我会
I think Andrew has been smoking marijuana,
我想Andrew一直在吸大麻
so I want you to take this and get it tested right away.
所以我想你拿上这个马上去检测一下
Why?
为什么？
Because I want you to pull him from the swim team,
我想让你不要让他去游泳队
and I don't think you'll allow it without proof.
我想如果没有证据你是不会那么做的
Proof or no proof, you're not going to take him off the team.
证据或者没有证据  你都不能 把他从游泳队弄回来
Yes, I am.
我会的
If you try, I'm going to go to the coach and tell him to ignore you.
如果你要那么做  我就告诉教练别理你
We're not going to screw up Andrew's future just because he sparked a doobie.
我们不能毁了Andrew的未来 就是因为他出点格
I mean, come on, we've all done it.
我的意思是  我们不是说好了吗
Not all of us.
并没有解决
Rex, I thought you moved back home to try and straighten Andrew out,
Rex  我以为你会回家并教育Andrew
to teach him the consequences of his actions.
告诉他所做事情的后果
I don't understand why you're fighting me on this.
我不明白你为什么总和我纠缠这事
Because I disagree, because we're still getting divorced,
因为我不同意  因为我们还没离婚
and I don't have to let you push me around anymore.
我不会在让你牵着我的鼻子
I never pushed you around.
我从来没有逼过你
We always made our decisions together.
我们总是一起做决定
No, you always make decisions, then tell me I agree.
不  你总是做好决定  让我同意
18 years of smiling and taking it -- what a liar I was.
18年来我都忍了  我撒了一个多大的谎
Thank god you're out of my life.
谢天谢地终于要摆脱你了
Rex.
Rex
What the hell are you doing?
你究竟在做什么呢
Same thing you just did to every memory I have of our marriage.
做我一直做的事情
You know what?
你知道吗？
If you were my mom, I'd smoke pot, too!
如果你是我妈  我也会吸大麻的
So your boss made you return her underwear?
那么你的顾主让你还她的内衣？
Yep, after she had already worn them once.
是的  结果她就穿了一次
Couldn't you have just said no?
你难道没有说不吗？
You don't say no to Alexis if you want to keep your job.
如果你想保住工作就不能对Alexis说不
She sounds awful.
她听起来很可怕啊
What can I do? I love the kids.
我能怎么办呢？我爱这些孩子
Boy, if we had a nanny like you at my house, we would treat her like gold.
如果我们家有你这样的保姆 我们高兴还来不及呢
Did I mention I have four very lovable kids?
我说过我有4个可爱的孩子吗？
Really?
真的吗？
Oh, yes.
噢  是的
Oh, no.
噢  不
What?
什么？
It's Alexis.
是Alexis
I don't want her to get the wrong idea, so you should go.
我不想让她误会  所以你还是走吧
Are you going to be here tomorrow? I want to see you again.
你明天还来这吗？我想再见到你
No. I'm busy.
不  我很忙
I just want to talk.
我只是想说说话
Lynette, this isn't right.
Lynette  这不行
Claire, Claire, please.
Claire  Claire求你了
All right.
好把
I will be at this address until noon tomorrow.
我会待再那直到明天中午
Now go.
走了
Okay.
好的
Hi. Where are the kids?
嘿  孩子呢？
What are you doing here?
你在这干什么？
I know you know,
我知道你明白的
and you're probably freaking out, so I just wanted to explain.
你可能被吓坏了  我想给你解释
What me and Mrs. Solis have --
我和Solis...
it's deep,
爱的很深
you know? We've got a future. It's not just sex.
你知道吗？我们有美好的未来  不只有性
Listen to me.
听我说
There is no future for you and Gabrielle.
你和Gabrielle是不会有结果的
She's not going to divorce Carlos and run away with you.
她不会和Carlos离婚和你私奔
Why not?
为什么不会呢？
Because he has money --a lot of it.
因为他有钱而且很多
Look, I'm not going to be mowing lawns forever.
听着  我不打算割一辈子的草坪
- I have big plans for my life.
- 我有很大的计划
Wow, okay.
啊  那好
You know, just stop talking.
听着  别说了
John, how old are you?
John  你多大了？
Almost 18.
快18了
Exactly.
那就对了
You are not mature enough to have a realistic perspective on this relationship.
你还太年轻  有这种关系 对你来说还不现实
You would be so much happier with a girl your own age.
你和你同龄的女孩在一起才会快乐
She's the one I want.
她就是我想要的
You know, I really love her.
你知道吗  我非常爱她
Please let's welcome Mrs. Arlene Nord!
让我们欢迎Arlene Nord夫人
We have Arlene and her husband Norris to thank for all our folding chairs this evening,
Arlene和她的丈夫Norris提供了今晚的 折叠凳子
so please remember for all your folding chair needs, rent Nord's.
所以请记住要买折叠椅子找Nord
Next up we have Mrs. Betty Nolan.
下一个是Betty Nolan夫人
Betty is looking...
Betty看起来...
Thank god Tom could fill in at the last minute.
谢天谢地Tom终于来了
Why did Carlos have to back out?
为什么Carlos缺席？
Some work emergency. He wouldn't talk about it.
工作上有点事  他不愿意说
Sometimes I could just kill him.
有时候真想杀了他
Well, look on the bright side -- Tom's having the time of his life.
看开点  Tom正在享受他的生活
Hands off, fellas. She's all mine.
手放下来吧  伙计们  她是我的了
I guess he does sort of have a dorky charm.
我猜他有某中魔力
Okay, Bree, you're up first,
噢  Bree  你是第一个
followed by Lynette.
Lynette跟上
Okay.
好的
Uh, and then Edie.
噢  然后是Edie
Edie. Where's Edie Britt?!
Edie  Edie Britt在哪？
Over here!
在这
Edie, what did you do to that dress?
Edie你的裙子怎么了？
Well, I made it audience-friendly.
这样比较吸引观众
Can you tell I'm not wearing any underwear?
我能不穿内衣吗？
Yes.
是的
Good.
太好了
Sorry I'm late.
对不起我来晚了
You should never take this dress off for your entire life.
你不应该再把它脱下来
Really? I look okay?
是吗？我看起来还行吧？
Oh, Susan, you look so gorgeous.
噢  Susan  你太美了
Doesn't she, Edie?
是吗  Edie？
Uh, it's a bit much.
哦  还说的过去
Gabrielle, you have to change the lineup.
Gabrielle  你应该换一下出场顺序
Susan has to go last. Nothing is going to top this.
Susan应该最后一个  没有人比她更合适
Oh, no, isn't Helen Rowland going last?
噢  不  Helen Rowland是最后一个？
Well, she never showed up. Somebody's got to take her place.
是的  她压根没来 得有人替她才行
Yeah, I think that's a great idea.
是啊  是个好主意
Okay, let's go.
好了  我们走
You really do look fantastic.
你真的太美了
Next up we have Mrs. Bree Van De Kamp
下一位是Bree Van De Kamp夫人
in a pink party dress with laser cut full skirt and silk belt.
穿着粉红裙子和丝织腰带
And here's another exquisite ball gown by Halston,
下面一位是穿Halston设计高贵舞会长袍
modeled by the devastatingly sexy Lynette Scavo.
模特是性感的 Lynette Scavo
Notice the fine detail,
注意细节
the clean lines...
精细的做工
the dress is nice, too.
你的裙子也非常漂亮
Next up, please welcome Edie...
下一位  请欢迎Edie
Britt.
Britt
Edie britt.
Edie britt
Please tell Gabrielle I'm sorry I backed out of the show.
请告诉 Gabrielle非常抱歉不能上场
I'm just not in a very festive mood right now.
现在我心情不好
Helen.
Helen
Helen, you're here.
Helen 　 你在这啊
Did they tell you about the change in the lineup?
她们没有告诉你已经换出场顺序了吗?
I'm going to go last. I hope that's okay.
我最后一个出场　希望不会发生什么
There's a special place in hell for people like you.
谁会喜欢你呢除了在地狱的人
I'm sorry. It wasn't my decision.
对不起那不是我的决定
You're an adult.
你已经是成人了
Take some responsibility.
请你注意点
What is wrong with you?
你是怎么了？
Edie is wearing a dignified classic,
Edie的衣服很有品位
perfect for a Sunday tea or christening.
非常适合喝茶或者洗礼日穿
For god's sake, Helen, this is for charity!
看在上帝的份上　 Helen 这是慈善拍卖用的
Edie Britt, everyone.
Edie Britt　每个人
Keep your hands off my son.
离我儿子远点
What?!
什么？
And, uh, finally, to cap off our evening...
噢　最后　我们的压轴的是...
Come on. You're on.
快点　该你了
Please welcome the radiant
请欢迎光彩照人的
Susan Mayer!
Susan Mayer！
Tom, say something.
Tom　说点什么
A vision in white silk,
看那白色丝绸
chiffon with gold,
金色的花边
hand-beaded french lace,
法国的手工珍珠饰品
and lavender marabou.
和熏衣草
Susan Mayer.
Susan Mayer
Oh, she's never looked better..
噢　她从没有这么漂亮...
Susan, I feel awful about what happened.
Susan　我感到非常抱歉
Susan, talk to me.
Susan　和我说点什么
Okay, you want me to talk?
好　你想我说什么？
You're going to find Helen Rowland, and you're going to tell her the truth
你去找 Helen Rowland　并告诉她真相
before everyone in this neighborhood thinks that I'm the one sleeping with an underage boy.
在邻居认为是我和那个 未成年男骇有染之前
I can't do that.
我不能那么做
Why not?
为什么不能？
Because she'll tell Carlos, and he'll divorce me.
她会给Carlos打电话　他会和我离婚
So what? You obviously don't love him.
那又怎么样？你又不爱他
I do love him. I-I do.
我是爱他的
It's just... complicated.
这有点复杂
You know? There's --
你知道吗？
there's got to be another way to fix this.
这一定还有其他方法解决
God. You are so weak.
上帝　你太软弱了
Susan, don't be like this.
Susan　不要这样
What did you expect, a hug?
你想要什么？一个拥抱
Hey.
嘿
Shh.
恩
I took --
我来
Alexis is still here.
Alexis仍在这
Oh.
噢
She was supposed to go to pilates, but she got her period.
她本来要去 pilates　但她来月经了
You got to go.
你赶紧走
Just give me a second.
就一会工夫
No. She saw you at the park, okay?
不行　她在公园见过你　好吗？
She knows what you're trying to do. You're not the first person to approach me.
她知道你要干什么 你已经不是第１个接近我的人了
Claire!
Claire！
How can you stay here after the way she treats you?
她这么对你你怎么还待在这？
She can be tough,
她有资格严厉
but it comes with the territory, right?
但这是她的地盘　对吗？
I would never treat you that way.
我不会那样对你
Claire, what did you do with the aspirin?!
Claire　你把 aspirin放哪了？
I will give you a 20% bump on what she's paying you, plus overtime.
我多给你增加２０％的工资 包括加班费
Damn it, Claire, where the hell are you?!
见鬼　 Claire　你跑哪去了？
I don't take orders from your friends,
我不听你朋友的使唤
I'm not a telephone answering service, and I don't do laundry.
我不是电话服务生 我不洗衣服
Dishes?
做饭呢？
Only the kids'.
仅做孩子的
How fast can you pack?
你能多快收拾好行李？
I got a nanny
我找到了一个保姆
Where are you going to go?
你准备去哪？
I don't know,
我不知道
but I can't go home.
但是不能回家
Are you afraid of your dad?
你怕你的父亲？
No, it's not him, all right?
不是因为他
It's -- it's me. My life is really messed up.
主要是我　我的生活一团糟
It's bad.
非常糟糕
What's bad? You can tell me.
有多坏？你能告诉我吗？
No, I can't.
不　我不能
It's better that you don't know.
你最好别知道
I already know a little.
我已经知道了一些
Hi, Danielle. How was school?
嘿　 Danielle　学校怎么样？
It was okay.
很好
Good. Where does Andrew keep his marijuana?
好　Andrew把大麻藏在哪了？
Bree had resorted to extreme measures to save her son's soul.
Bree采取了最极端方法来 拯救她的儿子的灵魂
As she rummaged through Andrew's private possessions,
当她搜查Andrew私人物品时
it occurred to her that sometimes a little betrayal
她发现了有时候一点惩罚
is good for the soul.
对他的心灵有好处
I was really young, like 4.
我那时还很小　大概４岁
I heard my mom and my dad yelling.
我听见我的父母吵架
I heard them yell my name...
我听见他们提我的名字
and hers.
和她的
Dana?
Dana？
Mm-hmm.
恩
So...
所以...
I went down to the room, and I saw them cleaning it up.
我走进那个房间　我看见他们正在擦洗
Cleaning what up?
擦洗什么？
Blood.
血迹
Was it Dana's?
Dana的？
I think so.
我想是
I couldn't remember this for the longest time, and then...
我把这些多忘了　直到...
my mom killed herself,
我妈妈自杀的时候
and I started having these dreams.
我就开始做这些梦
I-I don't even see Dana.
我看不清楚Dana
I just -- I- I see --I see the blood
我只是看到了血
and my mom picking me up
我的妈妈抱起我
and putting --putting me on my bed and whispering that it's not my fault.
把我放在了床上 小声给我说那不是我的错
But after that, every time I'd say her name, they'd get upset.
但是从那以后　我一提她的名字 他们就非常生气
I wasn't even allowed to say it anymore.
我不允许再说她的名字
I'm not sure I understand what you're saying.
我不是太明白你说的
I killed my baby sister.
我杀了还是婴儿的妹妹
Zach, oh, my god.
Zach　噢　天那
And they buried her
然后他们就埋了她
to protect me.
为了保护我
Helen. Do you have a minute?
Helen　你有时间吗？
Oh, Gabrielle,
噢　Gabrielle
I didn't get a chance to tell you how sorry I was about what happened at the fundraiser.
我没有机会告诉你 那次慈善晚会出了什么事
I didn't intend to cause a scene.
我不想那么做的
No, it's okay. People didn't even notice.
不过还好　人们并没有注意
Well, this is a little awkward.
是的　有点尴尬
I-I know you're friends with Susan Mayer,
我知道你和 Susan Mayer是朋友
but let's just say I had my reasons.
但是我有我的理由
It wasn't Susan.
那不是Susan
It was me.
那是我
What?
什么？
I'm the one who was sleeping with your son.
我才是和你儿子有染的人
I'm so sorry.
对不起
For how long?
多久了？
Almost a year.
大约１年
But it's over now.
但是现在已经结束了
So when it started, he was...16?
当那开始的时候　他只有１６岁
I think.
我想
But, Helen, y-you have to believe me -- it's over now.
但是　Helen　请你相信我 这一切都结束了
No, you're wrong.
不　你错了
It's not even close to being over.
这事没完
Hey, coach wants to see you.
嘿　教练想见你
Really?
真的吗？
Hey, I bet it's about my scholarship.
嘿　我打赌是关于我奖学金的事
Hello?
你好？
Yes, this is she.
是　我就是
Marijuana in his locker? Oh, I'm just horrified.
在他的存物柜里发现了大麻？ 噢　我感到太吃惊了
There must be some sort of terrible mistake.
这可能是非常可怕的错误
Um, yeah, okay. Well, I will be right down.
好的　我现在就去
Elsewhere, another, darker secret was the object of an investigation.
在别处　另外一个秘密也在被调查
Mr. Linder.
Linder先生
Mr. Linder!
Huh?
恩？
Detective Beckerman. This is detective Burnett.
探员 Beckerman　这是探员 Burnett
We were hoping for a minute of your time.
我们希望和你聊几分钟
If you know anything about Zach's whereabouts, you need to tell me now.
如果你知道 Zach的下落 你有责任告诉我们
Um...
恩...
honey, what's going on?
亲爱的　怎么了？
Zach's gone from Silvercrest.
Zach从 Silvercrest跑了
They found letters in his room --
他们在他的房间发现了信件
letters from julie.
是 julie写的
Well, yes, they were writing to each other.
是的　他们一直在通信
I need to see those letters.
我需要那些信
Mom, they're private.
妈妈　那是私人物品
My son is missing.
我的儿子失踪了
Julie, in the letters, did Zach say anything about running away?
Julie　在那些信里Zach 有没有说逃跑的事请
No.
没有
There's your answer.
这是你的答案
Susan --
Susan
if we hear anything, I will let you know right away.
如果我们听到什么　我会立刻通知你
I understand how worried you must be.
我明白你很担心
Obviously, you don't.
很显然　你不明白
Paul, my daughter doesn't lie.
Paul　我的女儿是不会撒谎的
This was a very popular design.
这在当时非常流行
I must have sold several hundred of these just like it about 10 years back.
在过去10年里我大概卖了100多个
Do you keep any kind of documentation?
你有任何纪录吗？
Yeah, I have a list of customers' names on file... somewhere.
是的　我有一个顾客名单
It's been a while.
那有很久以前的事了
We'll need a copy of that list.
我们需要一份副本
Oh, sure.
噢　当然
Wow, this chest looks like it's been through hell.
啊　这个箱子怎么成这样了
Yeah, we pulled it out of Rockwater Lake.
是啊　我们才在 Rockwater湖里发现的
You could say by way of hell, considering.
你应该好好考虑一下
W-was there anything in the chest?
盒子里面有什么呢？
It had a body inside --
有一具尸体
adult female.
女尸
Yeah, but -- how do you fit a body into a chest that size?
是　但是你怎么能把尸体 装在这么大点的盒子里呢？
It was chopped up.
她被分尸了
Of all the stupid, boneheaded decisions.
这一切的愚蠢决定
What were you thinking?
你当时怎么想的？
I was set up, all right?
我被开除了　行了把？
The coach got an anonymous phone call.
有人给教练打了匿名电话
Andrew, what does it matter? The pot was there.
Andrew　那是怎么回事？ 你把大麻放在那里
I was holding it for a friend.
我是帮朋友放的
You know...
你知道吗...
I can't decide which is more humiliating --
我不知道哪个让我丢脸
the fact that my son got caught with pot in his locker
事实上我的儿子因藏毒被抓
or that he can't even come up with a decent enough lie to explain it.
或者是他没有一个合理的 理由来解释这一切
Gabrielle believed there was an excellent chance
Gabrielle相信那本是一个好机会
Helen Rowland would inform Carlos of his wife's extramarital activities.
Helen Rowland一定会告诉 Carlos整件事
Gabrielle knew she had to come clean.
Gabrielle知道她必须澄清此事
Carlos?
Carlos？
Yeah?
什么？
But coming clean...
但是澄清...
I, uh...
我  恩...
was not one of Gabrielle's specialties.
Gabrielle并不擅长那个
I'm going to bed.
我上床了
Thanks for the news flash.
谢谢你来告诉我
She turned me in.
她出卖我
Carlos!
Carlos！
Carlos, I'm so sorry. I am so sorry.
Carlos非常对不起  非常对不起
Sorry for what?
为什么道歉？
Just know that whatever happens, I love you very, very much.
不管发生什么事情　我都非常爱你
FBI. Open the door.
FBI  开门
Oh, my god.
噢  天那
FBI. If you do not open the door,
FBI  如果你不开门
I am authorized to enter the premises by use of force.
我有权使用武力
Carlos Solis, I have a warrant for your arrest.
Carlos Solis  我有拘捕令  你被捕了
You have the right to remain silent.
你有权保持沉默
Huh?
恩？
Anything you say can and will be used against you in a court of law.
你所说的将作为呈堂证供
Call our lawyer.
叫我们的律师
You have the right to speak with an attorney...
你有权请律师...
- And have an attorney present during questioning.
- 在审讯时律师可以在场
Carlos. what's happening?
Carlos　发生什么事情了
If you cannot afford a lawyer, one will be appointed for you at government expense.
如果你请不起律师 我们会给你免费提供一个
Carlos, wait!
Carlos  等等！
Gabrielle, this will all be taken care of, I promise.
Gabrielle  我保证会没事的
I-I'm innocent, I swear to god.
我向上帝发誓  我是无辜的
It was Tanaka. He set me up.
是 Tanaka 陷害我的
People are complicated creatures.
人是一种复杂的动物
On the one hand, able to perform great acts of charity.
在一方面　在施舍方面表现很好
On the other...
另一方面...
capable of the most underhanded forms of betrayal.
却糟别人的背叛
It's a constant battle that rages within all of us
我们每个人的愤怒是一场持久战
between the better angels of our nature
在我们本性好的一面
and the temptation of our inner demons.
和我们内心深处的黑暗面
And sometimes, the only way to ward off the darkness...
有时候　唯一方法摆脱黑暗
is to shine the light of compassion.
就是要有点同情心
They took him away in handcuffs.
他们把他带走了　还带着手铐